<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Homegrown &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/homegrown/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 06:00:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Homegrown: Where to From Here</title>
		<link>/event/homegrown-where-to-from-here/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 23:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4718</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Where to from Here is a unique, multi-arts installation collaboration between contemporary artist Nicole Voevodin-Cash and photographer Teddy Horton, the work intervenes in the &#8216;end of life&#8217; journey of mattresses from the Sunshine Coast’s hospitality sector. 1.8 million mattresses are discarded each year in Australia, with around 33,000 tonnes ending up in landfill. This experimental &#8230; <a href="/event/homegrown-where-to-from-here/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Where to from Here is a unique, multi-arts installation collaboration between contemporary artist Nicole Voevodin-Cash and photographer Teddy Horton, the work intervenes in the &lsquo;end of life&rsquo; journey of mattresses from the Sunshine Coast&rsquo;s hospitality sector. 1.8 million mattresses are discarded each year in Australia, with around 33,000 tonnes ending up in landfill.</p>
<p><a href="/event/homegrown-where-to-from-here/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Homegrown: The Blak Laundry</title>
		<link>/event/homegrown-the-blak-laundry/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 22:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4713</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Blak Laundry is a functional laundromat — and exhibition space — for conversation, collaboration and celebration of all things Blak. Activated by Libby Harward and Dominique Chen, the concept is simple: bring your dirty linen, pop it on a warm wash, and engage in critical conversation whilst it cleans. In The Blak Laundry, everything &#8230; <a href="/event/homegrown-the-blak-laundry/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Blak Laundry is a functional laundromat &mdash; and exhibition space &mdash; for conversation, collaboration and celebration of all things Blak. Activated by Libby Harward and Dominique Chen, the concept is simple: bring your dirty linen, pop it on a warm wash, and engage in critical conversation whilst it cleans. In The Blak Laundry, everything comes out in the wash. The exhibition and laundromat are...</p>
<p><a href="/event/homegrown-the-blak-laundry/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Homegrown: Labyrinth</title>
		<link>/event/homegrown-labyrinth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 05:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4698</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Two lonely booksellers find themselves standing on the edge of eternity hurtling towards the end of all things. Together in their isolation, they spend their days frantically unearthing and preserving the last remnants of the books that remain. Bouncing between memory and reality, they repaint a picture of times gone by honouring the heartbreaking beauty &#8230; <a href="/event/homegrown-labyrinth/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two lonely booksellers find themselves standing on the edge of eternity hurtling towards the end of all things. Together in their isolation, they spend their days frantically unearthing and preserving the last remnants of the books that remain. Bouncing between memory and reality, they repaint a picture of times gone by honouring the heartbreaking beauty and fragility of this lost world.</p>
<p><a href="/event/homegrown-labyrinth/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
