<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Free &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/free/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 06:59:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Sunshine Coast Art Prize 2023</title>
		<link>/event/sunshine-coast-art-prize-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4879</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Regional Gallery of the Sunshine Coast presents a dynamic exhibition program featuring leading national and local artists, complemented by immersive public programs, educational programs, tours, and events. The Gallery Store highlights regional and national artisans, with a focus on local, hand-crafted items and a curated Pop-Up Feature Artisan program with every exhibition. The national &#8230; <a href="/event/sunshine-coast-art-prize-2023/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Regional Gallery of the Sunshine Coast presents a dynamic exhibition program featuring leading national and local artists, complemented by immersive public programs, educational programs, tours, and events. The Gallery Store highlights regional and national artisans, with a focus on local, hand-crafted items and a curated Pop-Up Feature Artisan program with every exhibition.</p>
<p><a href="/event/sunshine-coast-art-prize-2023/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Superpowered on Tour</title>
		<link>/event/superpowered-on-tour/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4868</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Experience the free ‘Superpowered on Tour’ program in the Festival Hub garden as part of Horizon Kids. This program will feature activities created by the Children’s Art Centre in collaboration with four Australian artists – Kaylene Whiskey (Yankunytjatjara people), Tony Albert (Girramay/Yidinyji/Kuku Yalanji peoples), Gordon Hookey (Waanyi people) and Vincent Namatjira (Western Aranda people) – &#8230; <a href="/event/superpowered-on-tour/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Experience the free &lsquo;Superpowered on Tour&rsquo; program in the Festival Hub garden as part of Horizon Kids. This program will feature activities created by the Children&rsquo;s Art Centre in collaboration with four Australian artists &ndash; Kaylene Whiskey (Yankunytjatjara people), Tony Albert (Girramay/Yidinyji/Kuku Yalanji peoples), Gordon Hookey (Waanyi people) and Vincent Namatjira (Western Aranda people)...</p>
<p><a href="/event/superpowered-on-tour/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jarjums Life Museum-Botanica</title>
		<link>/event/jarjums-life-museum-botanica/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 23:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4858</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Deep dive into the floral worlds of Jinibara and Kabi Kabi Country with Jarjum Life Museum’s Botanica work. Popping up at the Festival Hub garden this family friendly space will explore, play, and create with the natural wonders of Country. Jarjum Life Museum (JLM): Botanica will connect with Traditional Owners, Elders, community members and jarjum &#8230; <a href="/event/jarjums-life-museum-botanica/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Deep dive into the floral worlds of Jinibara and Kabi Kabi Country with Jarjum Life Museum&rsquo;s Botanica work. Popping up at the Festival Hub garden this family friendly space will explore, play, and create with the natural wonders of Country. Jarjum Life Museum (JLM): Botanica will connect with Traditional Owners, Elders, community members and jarjum to create a hands-on...</p>
<p><a href="/event/jarjums-life-museum-botanica/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Story time with Codie &#038; Ryan</title>
		<link>/event/story-time-with-codie-ryan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 22:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4850</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Join Codie and Ryan from Sunshine Coast Libraries for a rousing story time aboard the Troubadour Wagon in the Festival Hub garden. Showcasing classic stories and rhymes plus a few new ones for you to discover. If you love a good story or rhyme, you’ve come to the right place — you and your little &#8230; <a href="/event/story-time-with-codie-ryan/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Join Codie and Ryan from Sunshine Coast Libraries for a rousing story time aboard the Troubadour Wagon in the Festival Hub garden. Showcasing classic stories and rhymes plus a few new ones for you to discover. If you love a good story or rhyme, you&rsquo;ve come to the right place &mdash; you and your little one are guaranteed lots of fun and laughter.</p>
<p><a href="/event/story-time-with-codie-ryan/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WARP</title>
		<link>/event/warp/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 10:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4839</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WARP is a Jack MacRae exhibition, presenting in an old abandoned jail. An explosion of distilled geometric forms, Jack’s new body of work takes on an expanded painting practice — rationalised, brutalised, explored, and expanded. Born from solitary, WARP is a raw, lost-in-thought and hopeful portrayal of what’s to come. Lock yourself in and throw &#8230; <a href="/event/warp/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WARP is a Jack MacRae exhibition, presenting in an old abandoned jail. An explosion of distilled geometric forms, Jack&rsquo;s new body of work takes on an expanded painting practice &mdash; rationalised, brutalised, explored, and expanded. Born from solitary, WARP is a raw, lost-in-thought and hopeful portrayal of what&rsquo;s to come. Lock yourself in and throw away the key. WARP will launch on the opening night...</p>
<p><a href="/event/warp/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dear Reader: a celebration of readers, writers and libraries</title>
		<link>/event/dear-reader-a-celebration-of-readers-writers-and-libraries/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 03:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4792</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Read, listen, learn and connect with your community over your shared love of literature.Sunshine Coast Council Libraries are bringing together writers, readers, and creatives to share the love of stories for one big day at the Beerwah Heart Precinct. Meet and mingle with successful local authors, join exciting storytelling sessions, hear compelling First Nations stories, &#8230; <a href="/event/dear-reader-a-celebration-of-readers-writers-and-libraries/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Read, listen, learn and connect with your community over your shared love of literature.Sunshine Coast Council Libraries are bringing together writers, readers, and creatives to share the love of stories for one big day at the Beerwah Heart Precinct. Meet and mingle with successful local authors, join exciting storytelling sessions, hear compelling First Nations stories, find your next great read...</p>
<p><a href="/event/dear-reader-a-celebration-of-readers-writers-and-libraries/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You Are Neither Here Nor There: Sam Cranstoun</title>
		<link>/event/you-are-neither-here-nor-there-sam-cranstoun/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 01:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4759</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You Are Neither Here Nor There brings together four projects made during the first decade of Queensland artist Sam Cranstoun’s research-driven practice. The subject matter reflects the artist’s interest in lesser-known aspects of significant twentieth-century figures and events. Mies Van Der Rohe’s Farnsworth House, the Memphis motel where Martin Luther King was assassinated, and the &#8230; <a href="/event/you-are-neither-here-nor-there-sam-cranstoun/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You Are Neither Here Nor There brings together four projects made during the first decade of Queensland artist Sam Cranstoun&rsquo;s research-driven practice. The subject matter reflects the artist&rsquo;s interest in lesser-known aspects of significant twentieth-century figures and events. Mies Van Der Rohe&rsquo;s Farnsworth House, the Memphis motel where Martin Luther King was assassinated, and the life of...</p>
<p><a href="/event/you-are-neither-here-nor-there-sam-cranstoun/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unapologetically Dressed</title>
		<link>/event/unapologetically-dressed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4750</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Unapologetically Dressed was born out of Mill Street Fashion Walk — an Instagram page dedicated to a necessity to document fashion on the streets of Nambour. Ketakii Jewson-Brown and Shaye Hardsity of ShayeKet Productions began scoping out the street style of Nambour back in 2019. As the fashion capital of the Sunshine Coast, Nambour’s streets &#8230; <a href="/event/unapologetically-dressed/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unapologetically Dressed was born out of Mill Street Fashion Walk &mdash; an Instagram page dedicated to a necessity to document fashion on the streets of Nambour. Ketakii Jewson-Brown and Shaye Hardsity of ShayeKet Productions began scoping out the street style of Nambour back in 2019. As the fashion capital of the Sunshine Coast, Nambour&rsquo;s streets showcase a visual smorgasbord full of eclectic...</p>
<p><a href="/event/unapologetically-dressed/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nonsensual</title>
		<link>/event/nonsensual/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4744</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Set your senses into overdrive with this wildly fun, colourful and absurd exhibition. Nonsensual is a non-censored and nonsensical art display. In layman’s terms: Nonsensual is an uncensored exhibition, featuring three unapologetic artists — Fat Dog, Spirit You, and Jordyn Burnett — on their journey for meaning in a world that makes no f**cking sense. &#8230; <a href="/event/nonsensual/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Set your senses into overdrive with this wildly fun, colourful and absurd exhibition. Nonsensual is a non-censored and nonsensical art display. In layman&rsquo;s terms: Nonsensual is an uncensored exhibition, featuring three unapologetic artists &mdash; Fat Dog, Spirit You, and Jordyn Burnett &mdash; on their journey for meaning in a world that makes no f**cking sense.</p>
<p><a href="/event/nonsensual/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Njumga Djum Yo: ran Ba Djuwan</title>
		<link>/event/njumga-djum-yoran-ba-djuwan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4740</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Translated to ‘through the smoke they come home,’ this moving visual art exhibition curated by prominent Jinibara artists explores the intricate connection between people and place and each of the featured artists are inspired by, and called to create, by country itself. From March of 1877 Jinibara country changed significantly for it marked the beginning &#8230; <a href="/event/njumga-djum-yoran-ba-djuwan/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Translated to &lsquo;through the smoke they come home,&rsquo; this moving visual art exhibition curated by prominent Jinibara artists explores the intricate connection between people and place and each of the featured artists are inspired by, and called to create, by country itself. From March of 1877 Jinibara country changed significantly for it marked the beginning of the first local aboriginal mission at...</p>
<p><a href="/event/njumga-djum-yoran-ba-djuwan/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
