<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Performance &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/performance/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 04:42:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>hotmess (sold out)</title>
		<link>/event/hotmess/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 23:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4862</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HOTMESS is a decadent life drawing experience designed to ignite your creative fire and release you from normality. Be prepared to be immersed in a fictional world of costume, sound, lighting and performance used to playfully nudge one to question the fabric of life through emotional experiences. HOTMESS thrives on the edge of exploring ideas &#8230; <a href="/event/hotmess/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HOTMESS is a decadent life drawing experience designed to ignite your creative fire and release you from normality. Be prepared to be immersed in a fictional world of costume, sound, lighting and performance used to playfully nudge one to question the fabric of life through emotional experiences. HOTMESS thrives on the edge of exploring ideas that are cheeky, evocative and conceptual...</p>
<p><a href="/event/hotmess/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Junior Burger Rock Show</title>
		<link>/event/junior-burger-rock-show/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 09:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4822</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Who says the adults get to have all the fun? Junior Burger is here to save you and your kids from boring kids music — replacing it with rad beats and tasty guitars that will make them kick the air, fist pump and go “ooooh yeeeaaaaah! Junior Burger is the brand new project from motorcycle &#8230; <a href="/event/junior-burger-rock-show/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Who says the adults get to have all the fun? Junior Burger is here to save you and your kids from boring kids music &mdash; replacing it with rad beats and tasty guitars that will make them kick the air, fist pump and go &ldquo;ooooh yeeeaaaaah! Junior Burger is the brand new project from motorcycle riding funklords Burger Joint and they&rsquo;ve decided it&rsquo;s about time the kids get a decent rock concert, too!</p>
<p><a href="/event/junior-burger-rock-show/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sunshine Coast Comedy Gala</title>
		<link>/event/sunshine-coast-comedy-gala/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 09:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4818</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Strap in for an exclusive and hilarious preview of what’s coming your way in November, with the Sunshine Coast Comedy Festival Gala in the Wonderland Spiegeltent. It’s a world-class evening of stand-up comedy, showcasing some of the most exciting acts and new talent you’ll see at the 2023 Sunshine Coast Comedy Festival. From the uniquely &#8230; <a href="/event/sunshine-coast-comedy-gala/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Strap in for an exclusive and hilarious preview of what&rsquo;s coming your way in November, with the Sunshine Coast Comedy Festival Gala in the Wonderland Spiegeltent. It&rsquo;s a world-class evening of stand-up comedy, showcasing some of the most exciting acts and new talent you&rsquo;ll see at the 2023 Sunshine Coast Comedy Festival. From the uniquely dark wit of ABC TV&rsquo;s Craig Quartermaine (&ldquo;Laugh-out-loud...</p>
<p><a href="/event/sunshine-coast-comedy-gala/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rouge</title>
		<link>/event/rouge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 09:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4812</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Circus for grown-ups: ROUGE is a decadent blend of sensational acrobatics, operatic cabaret, and tongue-in-cheek burlesque. All the spectacle of a circus with a deliciously deviant, adults-only twist — ROUGE is a mind-bending blend of death-defying acrobatics, grandiose cabaret and deeply twisted burlesque. A titillating celebration of astonishing proportions that’s surprising, subversive, and supremely sexy. &#8230; <a href="/event/rouge/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Circus for grown-ups: ROUGE is a decadent blend of sensational acrobatics, operatic cabaret, and tongue-in-cheek burlesque. All the spectacle of a circus with a deliciously deviant, adults-only twist &mdash; ROUGE is a mind-bending blend of death-defying acrobatics, grandiose cabaret and deeply twisted burlesque. A titillating celebration of astonishing proportions that&rsquo;s surprising, subversive...</p>
<p><a href="/event/rouge/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circus Wonderland: A Neverland Adventure</title>
		<link>/event/circus-wonderland-a-neverland-adventure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 09:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4807</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Are you ready to go back to Neverland with JM Barrie&#8217;s classic story about Peter Pan, Wendy, Tinker Bell, pirates, mermaids and a ticking crocodile? Think your happy thoughts and get ready to take the second star to the right and head straight on till morning to ‘A Neverland Adventure’. Be amazed and captivated as &#8230; <a href="/event/circus-wonderland-a-neverland-adventure/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you ready to go back to Neverland with JM Barrie&rsquo;s classic story about Peter Pan, Wendy, Tinker Bell, pirates, mermaids and a ticking crocodile? Think your happy thoughts and get ready to take the second star to the right and head straight on till morning to &lsquo;A Neverland Adventure&rsquo;. Be amazed and captivated as you are immersed in the fantastical world of Neverland and the Mermaid Cove.</p>
<p><a href="/event/circus-wonderland-a-neverland-adventure/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Outhouse</title>
		<link>/event/the-outhouse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 04:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4802</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Outhouse will take you on an interactive journey into the ridiculous and sublime. Meet Hope and Luna.  Two clowns launching into outer space in their outhouse rocket to give planet earth the rest and rejuvenation she needs.  This two-woman physical comedy for all ages combines clown, shadow puppetry and animation to create an experience &#8230; <a href="/event/the-outhouse/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Outhouse will take you on an interactive journey into the ridiculous and sublime. Meet Hope and Luna. Two clowns launching into outer space in their outhouse rocket to give planet earth the rest and rejuvenation she needs. This two-woman physical comedy for all ages combines clown, shadow puppetry and animation to create an experience that will touch your heart and make your spirits soar.</p>
<p><a href="/event/the-outhouse/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sunshine Sounds Festival</title>
		<link>/event/sunshine-sounds-festival/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 04:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4798</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you need a little sunshine in your life, put the weekend of September 2 and 3 in your diary because Eumundi’s all-ages family-friendly music festival Sunshine Sounds is back as part of Horizon Festival. Come soak up the big-hearted groove of this special little festival, taking place in the historic School of Arts Hall on Gubbi &#8230; <a href="/event/sunshine-sounds-festival/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you need a little sunshine in your life, put the weekend of September 2 and 3 in your diary because Eumundi&rsquo;s all-ages family-friendly music festival Sunshine Sounds is back as part of Horizon Festival. Come soak up the big-hearted groove of this special little festival, taking place in the historic School of Arts Hall on Gubbi Gubbi country in the creative heartland of Eumundi.</p>
<p><a href="/event/sunshine-sounds-festival/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blak Social Party</title>
		<link>/event/blak-social-party/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 03:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4785</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Blak Social are throwing a deadly party to celebrate Blak Music and the First Nations artists who are the past, present and future of music in this continent. Come be with mob and show your love for Blak icons The Last Kinection as they perform alongside GLVES, Ethan Enoch and Djanabain this incredible Blak Social &#8230; <a href="/event/blak-social-party/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blak Social are throwing a deadly party to celebrate Blak Music and the First Nations artists who are the past, present and future of music in this continent. Come be with mob and show your love for Blak icons The Last Kinection as they perform alongside GLVES, Ethan Enoch and Djanabain this incredible Blak Social Party lineup. Blak Social is an Indigenous arts collective dreamed into existence by...</p>
<p><a href="/event/blak-social-party/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tallo-Billa (sold out)</title>
		<link>/event/tallo-billa/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 02:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4781</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[For Horizon Festival 2023, the Beeyali team invites attendees on a dusk ocean journey on board Sunreef’s Whale One, to listen underwater and experience cymatic visualisations of humpback whale songs. The field trip commences in Mooloolaba, where humpback whales annually migrate and rear their calves before returning to Antarctic waters and concludes with an original &#8230; <a href="/event/tallo-billa/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For Horizon Festival 2023, the Beeyali team invites attendees on a dusk ocean journey on board Sunreef&rsquo;s Whale One, to listen underwater and experience cymatic visualisations of humpback whale songs. The field trip commences in Mooloolaba, where humpback whales annually migrate and rear their calves before returning to Antarctic waters and concludes with an original immersive experience of the new...</p>
<p><a href="/event/tallo-billa/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Rations to Wages to Treaty</title>
		<link>/event/from-rations-to-wages-to-treaty/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 01:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4765</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[First Nations singer songwriter, Uncle Joe Geia and his band combine his songs, video, and storytelling to warmly introduce audiences to the lives of some of Australia’s most important and influential Indigenous leaders. Geia’s authenticity, reputation, and experience make such a telling possible. This musician’s musician has walked the story. Through his show From Rations &#8230; <a href="/event/from-rations-to-wages-to-treaty/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>First Nations singer songwriter, Uncle Joe Geia and his band combine his songs, video, and storytelling to warmly introduce audiences to the lives of some of Australia&rsquo;s most important and influential Indigenous leaders. Geia&rsquo;s authenticity, reputation, and experience make such a telling possible. This musician&rsquo;s musician has walked the story. Through his show From Rations To Wages To Treaty...</p>
<p><a href="/event/from-rations-to-wages-to-treaty/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
