<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Workshops &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/workshops/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 05:56:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Oriana Choir: A Weekend with Graham Abbott — concert</title>
		<link>/event/oriana-choir-a-weekend-with-graham-abbott-concert/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 03:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=5340</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A concert performance of select choruses from Handel&#8217;s Messiah and Mendelssohn&#8217;s Elijah. You are invited to this end of workshop, concert performance of select choruses from Handel&#8217;s Messiah and Mendelssohn&#8217;s Elijah. Directed by acclaimed conductor and choral director Graham Abbott, come and celebrate this beautiful music performed by the workshop participants. Interested in performing in &#8230; <a href="/event/oriana-choir-a-weekend-with-graham-abbott-concert/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A concert performance of select choruses from Handel&rsquo;s Messiah and Mendelssohn&rsquo;s Elijah. You are invited to this end of workshop, concert performance of select choruses from Handel&rsquo;s Messiah and Mendelssohn&rsquo;s Elijah. Directed by acclaimed conductor and choral director Graham Abbott, come and celebrate this beautiful music performed by the workshop participants. Interested in performing in the...</p>
<p><a href="/event/oriana-choir-a-weekend-with-graham-abbott-concert/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Skateboard Art Workshop</title>
		<link>/event/skateboard-art-workshop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4874</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Paint your own skateboard, whether you skate or don’t! This workshop is suitable for a solo mission/opportunity to meet new people, a date night between lovers or friends and everyone else in between. All materials provided, just bring yourself! About the Artist Fat Dog transcends the mundane through creation, typically with acrylic on skateboards.  A &#8230; <a href="/event/skateboard-art-workshop/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Paint your own skateboard, whether you skate or don&rsquo;t! This workshop is suitable for a solo mission/opportunity to meet new people, a date night between lovers or friends and everyone else in between. All materials provided, just bring yourself! Fat Dog transcends the mundane through creation, typically with acrylic on skateboards. A wildly fun and colourful caricaturist who exudes a passion for...</p>
<p><a href="/event/skateboard-art-workshop/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>hotmess (sold out)</title>
		<link>/event/hotmess/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 23:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4862</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HOTMESS is a decadent life drawing experience designed to ignite your creative fire and release you from normality. Be prepared to be immersed in a fictional world of costume, sound, lighting and performance used to playfully nudge one to question the fabric of life through emotional experiences. HOTMESS thrives on the edge of exploring ideas &#8230; <a href="/event/hotmess/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HOTMESS is a decadent life drawing experience designed to ignite your creative fire and release you from normality. Be prepared to be immersed in a fictional world of costume, sound, lighting and performance used to playfully nudge one to question the fabric of life through emotional experiences. HOTMESS thrives on the edge of exploring ideas that are cheeky, evocative and conceptual...</p>
<p><a href="/event/hotmess/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circus Skills Workshop (sold out)</title>
		<link>/event/circus-skills-workshop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 23:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4854</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Join us in the Festival Hub garden for a Circus workshop filled with fun and play! Fancy hula hoops, spinning plates, diablos, juggling and more!? Come and have fun and learn some new circus skills! CREATIVE TEAM Phoebe Manning Sarah Whitehead ABOUT THE ARTISTS Phoebe Manning and Sarah Whitehead are physical theatre performers based in &#8230; <a href="/event/circus-skills-workshop/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Join us in the Festival Hub garden for a Circus workshop filled with fun and play! Fancy hula hoops, spinning plates, diablos, juggling and more!? Come and have fun and learn some new circus skills! Phoebe Manning and Sarah Whitehead are physical theatre performers based in Meanjin. They are passionate about creating multi-disciplinary, accessible work that builds community and fosters connection.</p>
<p><a href="/event/circus-skills-workshop/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oriana Choir: A Weekend with Graham Abbott — workshop</title>
		<link>/event/a-weekend-with-graham-abbott/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 10:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4826</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Oriana Arts Inc. is hosting their second annual choral singing workshop, A Weekend with Graham Abbott. Graham Abbott has been Conductor-in-Residence at the Elder Conservatorium of Music Adelaide, Musical Director of Adelaide Philharmonia Chorus, Associate Conductor of the Melbourne Symphony Orchestra, Musical Director of Melbourne Chorale, and Guest Chorus Master for the Royal Scottish National &#8230; <a href="/event/a-weekend-with-graham-abbott/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Oriana Arts Inc. is hosting their second annual choral singing workshop, A Weekend with Graham Abbott. Graham Abbott has been Conductor-in-Residence at the Elder Conservatorium of Music Adelaide, Musical Director of Adelaide Philharmonia Chorus, Associate Conductor of the Melbourne Symphony Orchestra, Musical Director of Melbourne Chorale, and Guest Chorus Master for the Royal Scottish National...</p>
<p><a href="/event/a-weekend-with-graham-abbott/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dear Reader: a celebration of readers, writers and libraries</title>
		<link>/event/dear-reader-a-celebration-of-readers-writers-and-libraries/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 03:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4792</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Read, listen, learn and connect with your community over your shared love of literature.Sunshine Coast Council Libraries are bringing together writers, readers, and creatives to share the love of stories for one big day at the Beerwah Heart Precinct. Meet and mingle with successful local authors, join exciting storytelling sessions, hear compelling First Nations stories, &#8230; <a href="/event/dear-reader-a-celebration-of-readers-writers-and-libraries/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Read, listen, learn and connect with your community over your shared love of literature.Sunshine Coast Council Libraries are bringing together writers, readers, and creatives to share the love of stories for one big day at the Beerwah Heart Precinct. Meet and mingle with successful local authors, join exciting storytelling sessions, hear compelling First Nations stories, find your next great read...</p>
<p><a href="/event/dear-reader-a-celebration-of-readers-writers-and-libraries/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Glambour (sold out)</title>
		<link>/event/glambour/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4754</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Glambour is the launch party for two exhibitions at The Old Ambo: Unapologetically Dressed and Nonsensual. Expect a night of glamour, drag, music, costumes, and a lip sync battle — don’t forget to dress up! The evening will be hosted by this lot, so you know it’ll be a hoot: Andrea Kirwin, Jess Harlen, Ketakii &#8230; <a href="/event/glambour/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Glambour is the launch party for two exhibitions at The Old Ambo: Unapologetically Dressed and Nonsensual. Expect a night of glamour, drag, music, costumes, and a lip sync battle &mdash; don&rsquo;t forget to dress up! The evening will be hosted by this lot, so you know it&rsquo;ll be a hoot: Andrea Kirwin, Jess Harlen, Ketakii Jewson-Brown, Shaye Hardisty, Fat Dog, Jordyn Burnett, Fiona Harding, and heaps more.</p>
<p><a href="/event/glambour/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bees</title>
		<link>/event/bees/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 05:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4686</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bees by Polyglot Theatre is a joyful, interactive work in which children are invited to join in and participate in the world of community, communication, wonder, and imagination. Explore a buzzing, humming hive of activity in the Festival Hub garden as three human-sized bees busy themselves in the creation of a community alongside children who &#8230; <a href="/event/bees/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bees by Polyglot Theatre is a joyful, interactive work in which children are invited to join in and participate in the world of community, communication, wonder, and imagination. Explore a buzzing, humming hive of activity in the Festival Hub garden as three human-sized bees busy themselves in the creation of a community alongside children who transform themselves into bees as they play.</p>
<p><a href="/event/bees/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Let’s Organise Your Leisure: Workshops</title>
		<link>/event/lets-organise-your-leisure-workshops/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4603</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ABOUT THE PROJECT Let’s Organise your Leisure (LOYL) is a participatory art project for everyone — friends, family, first dates, tenth dates, seniors, students, and everyone in between. Join artist Kathy Mackey on a guided walk along the water’s edge at Maroochydore River to discover natural and pre-planted man-made materials commonly associated with leisure activities, such &#8230; <a href="/event/lets-organise-your-leisure-workshops/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Let&rsquo;s Organise your Leisure (LOYL) is a participatory art project for everyone &mdash; friends, family, first dates, tenth dates, seniors, students, and everyone in between. Join artist Kathy Mackey on a guided walk along the water&rsquo;s edge at Maroochydore River to discover natural and pre-planted man-made materials commonly associated with leisure activities, such as pool noodles and yoga mats.</p>
<p><a href="/event/lets-organise-your-leisure-workshops/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
