<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Music &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/music/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 13:13:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Oriana Choir: A Weekend with Graham Abbott — concert</title>
		<link>/event/oriana-choir-a-weekend-with-graham-abbott-concert/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 03:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=5340</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A concert performance of select choruses from Handel&#8217;s Messiah and Mendelssohn&#8217;s Elijah. You are invited to this end of workshop, concert performance of select choruses from Handel&#8217;s Messiah and Mendelssohn&#8217;s Elijah. Directed by acclaimed conductor and choral director Graham Abbott, come and celebrate this beautiful music performed by the workshop participants. Interested in performing in &#8230; <a href="/event/oriana-choir-a-weekend-with-graham-abbott-concert/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A concert performance of select choruses from Handel&rsquo;s Messiah and Mendelssohn&rsquo;s Elijah. You are invited to this end of workshop, concert performance of select choruses from Handel&rsquo;s Messiah and Mendelssohn&rsquo;s Elijah. Directed by acclaimed conductor and choral director Graham Abbott, come and celebrate this beautiful music performed by the workshop participants. Interested in performing in the...</p>
<p><a href="/event/oriana-choir-a-weekend-with-graham-abbott-concert/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oriana Choir: A Weekend with Graham Abbott — workshop</title>
		<link>/event/a-weekend-with-graham-abbott/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 10:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4826</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Oriana Arts Inc. is hosting their second annual choral singing workshop, A Weekend with Graham Abbott. Graham Abbott has been Conductor-in-Residence at the Elder Conservatorium of Music Adelaide, Musical Director of Adelaide Philharmonia Chorus, Associate Conductor of the Melbourne Symphony Orchestra, Musical Director of Melbourne Chorale, and Guest Chorus Master for the Royal Scottish National &#8230; <a href="/event/a-weekend-with-graham-abbott/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Oriana Arts Inc. is hosting their second annual choral singing workshop, A Weekend with Graham Abbott. Graham Abbott has been Conductor-in-Residence at the Elder Conservatorium of Music Adelaide, Musical Director of Adelaide Philharmonia Chorus, Associate Conductor of the Melbourne Symphony Orchestra, Musical Director of Melbourne Chorale, and Guest Chorus Master for the Royal Scottish National...</p>
<p><a href="/event/a-weekend-with-graham-abbott/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Junior Burger Rock Show</title>
		<link>/event/junior-burger-rock-show/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 09:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4822</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Who says the adults get to have all the fun? Junior Burger is here to save you and your kids from boring kids music — replacing it with rad beats and tasty guitars that will make them kick the air, fist pump and go “ooooh yeeeaaaaah! Junior Burger is the brand new project from motorcycle &#8230; <a href="/event/junior-burger-rock-show/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Who says the adults get to have all the fun? Junior Burger is here to save you and your kids from boring kids music &mdash; replacing it with rad beats and tasty guitars that will make them kick the air, fist pump and go &ldquo;ooooh yeeeaaaaah! Junior Burger is the brand new project from motorcycle riding funklords Burger Joint and they&rsquo;ve decided it&rsquo;s about time the kids get a decent rock concert, too!</p>
<p><a href="/event/junior-burger-rock-show/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sunshine Sounds Festival</title>
		<link>/event/sunshine-sounds-festival/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 04:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4798</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you need a little sunshine in your life, put the weekend of September 2 and 3 in your diary because Eumundi’s all-ages family-friendly music festival Sunshine Sounds is back as part of Horizon Festival. Come soak up the big-hearted groove of this special little festival, taking place in the historic School of Arts Hall on Gubbi &#8230; <a href="/event/sunshine-sounds-festival/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you need a little sunshine in your life, put the weekend of September 2 and 3 in your diary because Eumundi&rsquo;s all-ages family-friendly music festival Sunshine Sounds is back as part of Horizon Festival. Come soak up the big-hearted groove of this special little festival, taking place in the historic School of Arts Hall on Gubbi Gubbi country in the creative heartland of Eumundi.</p>
<p><a href="/event/sunshine-sounds-festival/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blak Social Party</title>
		<link>/event/blak-social-party/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 03:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4785</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Blak Social are throwing a deadly party to celebrate Blak Music and the First Nations artists who are the past, present and future of music in this continent. Come be with mob and show your love for Blak icons The Last Kinection as they perform alongside GLVES, Ethan Enoch and Djanabain this incredible Blak Social &#8230; <a href="/event/blak-social-party/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blak Social are throwing a deadly party to celebrate Blak Music and the First Nations artists who are the past, present and future of music in this continent. Come be with mob and show your love for Blak icons The Last Kinection as they perform alongside GLVES, Ethan Enoch and Djanabain this incredible Blak Social Party lineup. Blak Social is an Indigenous arts collective dreamed into existence by...</p>
<p><a href="/event/blak-social-party/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Rations to Wages to Treaty</title>
		<link>/event/from-rations-to-wages-to-treaty/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 01:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4765</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[First Nations singer songwriter, Uncle Joe Geia and his band combine his songs, video, and storytelling to warmly introduce audiences to the lives of some of Australia’s most important and influential Indigenous leaders. Geia’s authenticity, reputation, and experience make such a telling possible. This musician’s musician has walked the story. Through his show From Rations &#8230; <a href="/event/from-rations-to-wages-to-treaty/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>First Nations singer songwriter, Uncle Joe Geia and his band combine his songs, video, and storytelling to warmly introduce audiences to the lives of some of Australia&rsquo;s most important and influential Indigenous leaders. Geia&rsquo;s authenticity, reputation, and experience make such a telling possible. This musician&rsquo;s musician has walked the story. Through his show From Rations To Wages To Treaty...</p>
<p><a href="/event/from-rations-to-wages-to-treaty/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Glambour (sold out)</title>
		<link>/event/glambour/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4754</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Glambour is the launch party for two exhibitions at The Old Ambo: Unapologetically Dressed and Nonsensual. Expect a night of glamour, drag, music, costumes, and a lip sync battle — don’t forget to dress up! The evening will be hosted by this lot, so you know it’ll be a hoot: Andrea Kirwin, Jess Harlen, Ketakii &#8230; <a href="/event/glambour/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Glambour is the launch party for two exhibitions at The Old Ambo: Unapologetically Dressed and Nonsensual. Expect a night of glamour, drag, music, costumes, and a lip sync battle &mdash; don&rsquo;t forget to dress up! The evening will be hosted by this lot, so you know it&rsquo;ll be a hoot: Andrea Kirwin, Jess Harlen, Ketakii Jewson-Brown, Shaye Hardisty, Fat Dog, Jordyn Burnett, Fiona Harding, and heaps more.</p>
<p><a href="/event/glambour/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dawn Awakening</title>
		<link>/event/dawn-awakening/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 23:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4731</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Gather with us along the banks of Stumers Creek in Coolum as the first light rises and the voices of First Peoples call in a new energy for these times. Together we will journey through story, dance, song, visual art projections, spoken word and fire installations, to reflect, strengthen and testify a flourishing connection to &#8230; <a href="/event/dawn-awakening/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gather with us along the banks of Stumers Creek in Coolum as the first light rises and the voices of First Peoples call in a new energy for these times. Together we will journey through story, dance, song, visual art projections, spoken word and fire installations, to reflect, strengthen and testify a flourishing connection to country, culture and each other. Stumers Creek Rd is closed for this...</p>
<p><a href="/event/dawn-awakening/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opening Ceremony</title>
		<link>/event/opening-ceremony/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 23:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4722</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As the sun sets, ground your feet, as we gather on the shores of the Maroochy River, to celebrate and pay our respects to Traditional Custodians of the waterways, coastal plains and hinterlands of the Sunshine Coast, the Kabi Kabi and Jinibara peoples, and open the eighth Horizon Festival 2023. Come, sit, reflect, and welcome &#8230; <a href="/event/opening-ceremony/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the sun sets, ground your feet, as we gather on the shores of the Maroochy River, to celebrate and pay our respects to Traditional Custodians of the waterways, coastal plains and hinterlands of the Sunshine Coast, the Kabi Kabi and Jinibara peoples, and open the eighth Horizon Festival 2023. Come, sit, reflect, and welcome the start of 10 days and nights of rich programming from across the...</p>
<p><a href="/event/opening-ceremony/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lior</title>
		<link>/event/lior-domini/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 05:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4692</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Come and see Lior perform an intimate sunset concert. This is a chance to hear acclaimed singer-songwriter Lior in a manner harking back to archetypal ‘salon’ concerts; where the audience and performers share an evening enjoying the connection that only proximity can offer. Lior burst on to the Australian music scene in 2005 with his &#8230; <a href="/event/lior-domini/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Come and see Lior perform an intimate sunset concert. This is a chance to hear acclaimed singer-songwriter Lior in a manner harking back to archetypal &lsquo;salon&rsquo; concerts; where the audience and performers share an evening enjoying the connection that only proximity can offer. Lior burst on to the Australian music scene in 2005 with his stunning debut album &lsquo;Autumn Flow&rsquo;.</p>
<p><a href="/event/lior-domini/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
