<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>First Nations &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/first-nations/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 13:13:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Jarjums Life Museum-Botanica</title>
		<link>/event/jarjums-life-museum-botanica/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 23:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4858</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Deep dive into the floral worlds of Jinibara and Kabi Kabi Country with Jarjum Life Museum’s Botanica work. Popping up at the Festival Hub garden this family friendly space will explore, play, and create with the natural wonders of Country. Jarjum Life Museum (JLM): Botanica will connect with Traditional Owners, Elders, community members and jarjum &#8230; <a href="/event/jarjums-life-museum-botanica/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Deep dive into the floral worlds of Jinibara and Kabi Kabi Country with Jarjum Life Museum&rsquo;s Botanica work. Popping up at the Festival Hub garden this family friendly space will explore, play, and create with the natural wonders of Country. Jarjum Life Museum (JLM): Botanica will connect with Traditional Owners, Elders, community members and jarjum to create a hands-on...</p>
<p><a href="/event/jarjums-life-museum-botanica/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dear Reader: a celebration of readers, writers and libraries</title>
		<link>/event/dear-reader-a-celebration-of-readers-writers-and-libraries/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 03:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4792</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Read, listen, learn and connect with your community over your shared love of literature.Sunshine Coast Council Libraries are bringing together writers, readers, and creatives to share the love of stories for one big day at the Beerwah Heart Precinct. Meet and mingle with successful local authors, join exciting storytelling sessions, hear compelling First Nations stories, &#8230; <a href="/event/dear-reader-a-celebration-of-readers-writers-and-libraries/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Read, listen, learn and connect with your community over your shared love of literature.Sunshine Coast Council Libraries are bringing together writers, readers, and creatives to share the love of stories for one big day at the Beerwah Heart Precinct. Meet and mingle with successful local authors, join exciting storytelling sessions, hear compelling First Nations stories, find your next great read...</p>
<p><a href="/event/dear-reader-a-celebration-of-readers-writers-and-libraries/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blak Social Party</title>
		<link>/event/blak-social-party/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 03:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4785</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Blak Social are throwing a deadly party to celebrate Blak Music and the First Nations artists who are the past, present and future of music in this continent. Come be with mob and show your love for Blak icons The Last Kinection as they perform alongside GLVES, Ethan Enoch and Djanabain this incredible Blak Social &#8230; <a href="/event/blak-social-party/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blak Social are throwing a deadly party to celebrate Blak Music and the First Nations artists who are the past, present and future of music in this continent. Come be with mob and show your love for Blak icons The Last Kinection as they perform alongside GLVES, Ethan Enoch and Djanabain this incredible Blak Social Party lineup. Blak Social is an Indigenous arts collective dreamed into existence by...</p>
<p><a href="/event/blak-social-party/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tallo-Billa (sold out)</title>
		<link>/event/tallo-billa/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 02:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4781</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[For Horizon Festival 2023, the Beeyali team invites attendees on a dusk ocean journey on board Sunreef’s Whale One, to listen underwater and experience cymatic visualisations of humpback whale songs. The field trip commences in Mooloolaba, where humpback whales annually migrate and rear their calves before returning to Antarctic waters and concludes with an original &#8230; <a href="/event/tallo-billa/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For Horizon Festival 2023, the Beeyali team invites attendees on a dusk ocean journey on board Sunreef&rsquo;s Whale One, to listen underwater and experience cymatic visualisations of humpback whale songs. The field trip commences in Mooloolaba, where humpback whales annually migrate and rear their calves before returning to Antarctic waters and concludes with an original immersive experience of the new...</p>
<p><a href="/event/tallo-billa/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tallo-Billa: Ocean Fieldtrip (sold out)</title>
		<link>/event/tallo-billa-ocean-fieldtrip/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 02:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4775</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Field Trip is an experimental national research symposium featuring creative practice at the intersection of art, science, technology and the environment. The creative team will introduce the experimental technology and collaborative methodologies underpinning the Beeyali project, creating an immersive audio-visual experience that highlights the interconnectivity of life within marine environments. Delving into the multifaceted processes and &#8230; <a href="/event/tallo-billa-ocean-fieldtrip/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Field Trip is an experimental national research symposium featuring creative practice at the intersection of art, science, technology and the environment. The creative team will introduce the experimental technology and collaborative methodologies underpinning the Beeyali project, creating an immersive audio-visual experience that highlights the interconnectivity of life within marine environments.</p>
<p><a href="/event/tallo-billa-ocean-fieldtrip/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Rations to Wages to Treaty</title>
		<link>/event/from-rations-to-wages-to-treaty/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 01:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4765</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[First Nations singer songwriter, Uncle Joe Geia and his band combine his songs, video, and storytelling to warmly introduce audiences to the lives of some of Australia’s most important and influential Indigenous leaders. Geia’s authenticity, reputation, and experience make such a telling possible. This musician’s musician has walked the story. Through his show From Rations &#8230; <a href="/event/from-rations-to-wages-to-treaty/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>First Nations singer songwriter, Uncle Joe Geia and his band combine his songs, video, and storytelling to warmly introduce audiences to the lives of some of Australia&rsquo;s most important and influential Indigenous leaders. Geia&rsquo;s authenticity, reputation, and experience make such a telling possible. This musician&rsquo;s musician has walked the story. Through his show From Rations To Wages To Treaty...</p>
<p><a href="/event/from-rations-to-wages-to-treaty/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Njumga Djum Yo: ran Ba Djuwan</title>
		<link>/event/njumga-djum-yoran-ba-djuwan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4740</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Translated to ‘through the smoke they come home,’ this moving visual art exhibition curated by prominent Jinibara artists explores the intricate connection between people and place and each of the featured artists are inspired by, and called to create, by country itself. From March of 1877 Jinibara country changed significantly for it marked the beginning &#8230; <a href="/event/njumga-djum-yoran-ba-djuwan/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Translated to &lsquo;through the smoke they come home,&rsquo; this moving visual art exhibition curated by prominent Jinibara artists explores the intricate connection between people and place and each of the featured artists are inspired by, and called to create, by country itself. From March of 1877 Jinibara country changed significantly for it marked the beginning of the first local aboriginal mission at...</p>
<p><a href="/event/njumga-djum-yoran-ba-djuwan/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kabi Kabi Connections</title>
		<link>/event/kabi-kabi-connections/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4736</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Kabi Kabi Connections is the union between time immemorial and the ephemeral, where sacred ways of knowing and being meet new technologies and the natural environment. Curated by knowledge keeper and artist, Helena Gulash and interdisciplinary artist James Muller, this immersive and meditative work illuminates the waters of the Maroochy River with the work of Traditional Custodians and visual arts &#8230; <a href="/event/kabi-kabi-connections/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kabi Kabi Connections is the union between time immemorial and the ephemeral, where sacred ways of knowing and being meet new technologies and the natural environment. Curated by knowledge keeper and artist, Helena Gulash and interdisciplinary artist James Muller, this immersive and meditative work illuminates the waters of the Maroochy River with the work of Traditional Custodians and visual arts...</p>
<p><a href="/event/kabi-kabi-connections/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dawn Awakening</title>
		<link>/event/dawn-awakening/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 23:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4731</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Gather with us along the banks of Stumers Creek in Coolum as the first light rises and the voices of First Peoples call in a new energy for these times. Together we will journey through story, dance, song, visual art projections, spoken word and fire installations, to reflect, strengthen and testify a flourishing connection to &#8230; <a href="/event/dawn-awakening/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gather with us along the banks of Stumers Creek in Coolum as the first light rises and the voices of First Peoples call in a new energy for these times. Together we will journey through story, dance, song, visual art projections, spoken word and fire installations, to reflect, strengthen and testify a flourishing connection to country, culture and each other. Stumers Creek Rd is closed for this...</p>
<p><a href="/event/dawn-awakening/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opening Ceremony</title>
		<link>/event/opening-ceremony/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 23:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4722</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As the sun sets, ground your feet, as we gather on the shores of the Maroochy River, to celebrate and pay our respects to Traditional Custodians of the waterways, coastal plains and hinterlands of the Sunshine Coast, the Kabi Kabi and Jinibara peoples, and open the eighth Horizon Festival 2023. Come, sit, reflect, and welcome &#8230; <a href="/event/opening-ceremony/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the sun sets, ground your feet, as we gather on the shores of the Maroochy River, to celebrate and pay our respects to Traditional Custodians of the waterways, coastal plains and hinterlands of the Sunshine Coast, the Kabi Kabi and Jinibara peoples, and open the eighth Horizon Festival 2023. Come, sit, reflect, and welcome the start of 10 days and nights of rich programming from across the...</p>
<p><a href="/event/opening-ceremony/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
