<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Kids + Family &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/family-friendly/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 06:59:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Sunshine Coast Art Prize 2023</title>
		<link>/event/sunshine-coast-art-prize-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4879</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Regional Gallery of the Sunshine Coast presents a dynamic exhibition program featuring leading national and local artists, complemented by immersive public programs, educational programs, tours, and events. The Gallery Store highlights regional and national artisans, with a focus on local, hand-crafted items and a curated Pop-Up Feature Artisan program with every exhibition. The national &#8230; <a href="/event/sunshine-coast-art-prize-2023/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Regional Gallery of the Sunshine Coast presents a dynamic exhibition program featuring leading national and local artists, complemented by immersive public programs, educational programs, tours, and events. The Gallery Store highlights regional and national artisans, with a focus on local, hand-crafted items and a curated Pop-Up Feature Artisan program with every exhibition.</p>
<p><a href="/event/sunshine-coast-art-prize-2023/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Superpowered on Tour</title>
		<link>/event/superpowered-on-tour/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4868</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Experience the free ‘Superpowered on Tour’ program in the Festival Hub garden as part of Horizon Kids. This program will feature activities created by the Children’s Art Centre in collaboration with four Australian artists – Kaylene Whiskey (Yankunytjatjara people), Tony Albert (Girramay/Yidinyji/Kuku Yalanji peoples), Gordon Hookey (Waanyi people) and Vincent Namatjira (Western Aranda people) – &#8230; <a href="/event/superpowered-on-tour/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Experience the free &lsquo;Superpowered on Tour&rsquo; program in the Festival Hub garden as part of Horizon Kids. This program will feature activities created by the Children&rsquo;s Art Centre in collaboration with four Australian artists &ndash; Kaylene Whiskey (Yankunytjatjara people), Tony Albert (Girramay/Yidinyji/Kuku Yalanji peoples), Gordon Hookey (Waanyi people) and Vincent Namatjira (Western Aranda people)...</p>
<p><a href="/event/superpowered-on-tour/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jarjums Life Museum-Botanica</title>
		<link>/event/jarjums-life-museum-botanica/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 23:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4858</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Deep dive into the floral worlds of Jinibara and Kabi Kabi Country with Jarjum Life Museum’s Botanica work. Popping up at the Festival Hub garden this family friendly space will explore, play, and create with the natural wonders of Country. Jarjum Life Museum (JLM): Botanica will connect with Traditional Owners, Elders, community members and jarjum &#8230; <a href="/event/jarjums-life-museum-botanica/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Deep dive into the floral worlds of Jinibara and Kabi Kabi Country with Jarjum Life Museum&rsquo;s Botanica work. Popping up at the Festival Hub garden this family friendly space will explore, play, and create with the natural wonders of Country. Jarjum Life Museum (JLM): Botanica will connect with Traditional Owners, Elders, community members and jarjum to create a hands-on...</p>
<p><a href="/event/jarjums-life-museum-botanica/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circus Skills Workshop (sold out)</title>
		<link>/event/circus-skills-workshop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 23:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4854</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Join us in the Festival Hub garden for a Circus workshop filled with fun and play! Fancy hula hoops, spinning plates, diablos, juggling and more!? Come and have fun and learn some new circus skills! CREATIVE TEAM Phoebe Manning Sarah Whitehead ABOUT THE ARTISTS Phoebe Manning and Sarah Whitehead are physical theatre performers based in &#8230; <a href="/event/circus-skills-workshop/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Join us in the Festival Hub garden for a Circus workshop filled with fun and play! Fancy hula hoops, spinning plates, diablos, juggling and more!? Come and have fun and learn some new circus skills! Phoebe Manning and Sarah Whitehead are physical theatre performers based in Meanjin. They are passionate about creating multi-disciplinary, accessible work that builds community and fosters connection.</p>
<p><a href="/event/circus-skills-workshop/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Story time with Codie &#038; Ryan</title>
		<link>/event/story-time-with-codie-ryan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 22:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4850</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Join Codie and Ryan from Sunshine Coast Libraries for a rousing story time aboard the Troubadour Wagon in the Festival Hub garden. Showcasing classic stories and rhymes plus a few new ones for you to discover. If you love a good story or rhyme, you’ve come to the right place — you and your little &#8230; <a href="/event/story-time-with-codie-ryan/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Join Codie and Ryan from Sunshine Coast Libraries for a rousing story time aboard the Troubadour Wagon in the Festival Hub garden. Showcasing classic stories and rhymes plus a few new ones for you to discover. If you love a good story or rhyme, you&rsquo;ve come to the right place &mdash; you and your little one are guaranteed lots of fun and laughter.</p>
<p><a href="/event/story-time-with-codie-ryan/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Junior Burger Rock Show</title>
		<link>/event/junior-burger-rock-show/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 09:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4822</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Who says the adults get to have all the fun? Junior Burger is here to save you and your kids from boring kids music — replacing it with rad beats and tasty guitars that will make them kick the air, fist pump and go “ooooh yeeeaaaaah! Junior Burger is the brand new project from motorcycle &#8230; <a href="/event/junior-burger-rock-show/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Who says the adults get to have all the fun? Junior Burger is here to save you and your kids from boring kids music &mdash; replacing it with rad beats and tasty guitars that will make them kick the air, fist pump and go &ldquo;ooooh yeeeaaaaah! Junior Burger is the brand new project from motorcycle riding funklords Burger Joint and they&rsquo;ve decided it&rsquo;s about time the kids get a decent rock concert, too!</p>
<p><a href="/event/junior-burger-rock-show/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circus Wonderland: A Neverland Adventure</title>
		<link>/event/circus-wonderland-a-neverland-adventure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 09:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4807</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Are you ready to go back to Neverland with JM Barrie&#8217;s classic story about Peter Pan, Wendy, Tinker Bell, pirates, mermaids and a ticking crocodile? Think your happy thoughts and get ready to take the second star to the right and head straight on till morning to ‘A Neverland Adventure’. Be amazed and captivated as &#8230; <a href="/event/circus-wonderland-a-neverland-adventure/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you ready to go back to Neverland with JM Barrie&rsquo;s classic story about Peter Pan, Wendy, Tinker Bell, pirates, mermaids and a ticking crocodile? Think your happy thoughts and get ready to take the second star to the right and head straight on till morning to &lsquo;A Neverland Adventure&rsquo;. Be amazed and captivated as you are immersed in the fantastical world of Neverland and the Mermaid Cove.</p>
<p><a href="/event/circus-wonderland-a-neverland-adventure/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Outhouse</title>
		<link>/event/the-outhouse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 04:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4802</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Outhouse will take you on an interactive journey into the ridiculous and sublime. Meet Hope and Luna.  Two clowns launching into outer space in their outhouse rocket to give planet earth the rest and rejuvenation she needs.  This two-woman physical comedy for all ages combines clown, shadow puppetry and animation to create an experience &#8230; <a href="/event/the-outhouse/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Outhouse will take you on an interactive journey into the ridiculous and sublime. Meet Hope and Luna. Two clowns launching into outer space in their outhouse rocket to give planet earth the rest and rejuvenation she needs. This two-woman physical comedy for all ages combines clown, shadow puppetry and animation to create an experience that will touch your heart and make your spirits soar.</p>
<p><a href="/event/the-outhouse/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sunshine Sounds Festival</title>
		<link>/event/sunshine-sounds-festival/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 04:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4798</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you need a little sunshine in your life, put the weekend of September 2 and 3 in your diary because Eumundi’s all-ages family-friendly music festival Sunshine Sounds is back as part of Horizon Festival. Come soak up the big-hearted groove of this special little festival, taking place in the historic School of Arts Hall on Gubbi &#8230; <a href="/event/sunshine-sounds-festival/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you need a little sunshine in your life, put the weekend of September 2 and 3 in your diary because Eumundi&rsquo;s all-ages family-friendly music festival Sunshine Sounds is back as part of Horizon Festival. Come soak up the big-hearted groove of this special little festival, taking place in the historic School of Arts Hall on Gubbi Gubbi country in the creative heartland of Eumundi.</p>
<p><a href="/event/sunshine-sounds-festival/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dear Reader: a celebration of readers, writers and libraries</title>
		<link>/event/dear-reader-a-celebration-of-readers-writers-and-libraries/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 03:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4792</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Read, listen, learn and connect with your community over your shared love of literature.Sunshine Coast Council Libraries are bringing together writers, readers, and creatives to share the love of stories for one big day at the Beerwah Heart Precinct. Meet and mingle with successful local authors, join exciting storytelling sessions, hear compelling First Nations stories, &#8230; <a href="/event/dear-reader-a-celebration-of-readers-writers-and-libraries/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Read, listen, learn and connect with your community over your shared love of literature.Sunshine Coast Council Libraries are bringing together writers, readers, and creatives to share the love of stories for one big day at the Beerwah Heart Precinct. Meet and mingle with successful local authors, join exciting storytelling sessions, hear compelling First Nations stories, find your next great read...</p>
<p><a href="/event/dear-reader-a-celebration-of-readers-writers-and-libraries/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
