<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Words + Ideas &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/words-ideas/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 02:18:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Critical Light</title>
		<link>/event/critical-light/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 23:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=5653</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Are you a highly engaged contemporary practitioner wanting to expand your critical appreciation of contemporary arts practices? Apply to participate in Critical Light here. Up to eight Sunshine Coast artists will journey Horizon Festival over the first weekend with curator, writer and researcher and Critical Light Provocateur Madeleine King, to shine a critical light on &#8230; <a href="/event/critical-light/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you a highly engaged contemporary practitioner wanting to expand your critical appreciation of contemporary arts practices? Up to eight Sunshine Coast artists will journey Horizon Festival over the first weekend with curator, writer and researcher and Critical Light Provocateur Madeleine King, to shine a critical light on the program through interpretation, contextualisation...</p>
<p><a href="/event/critical-light/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jarjums Life Museum-Botanica</title>
		<link>/event/jarjums-life-museum-botanica/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 23:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4858</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Deep dive into the floral worlds of Jinibara and Kabi Kabi Country with Jarjum Life Museum’s Botanica work. Popping up at the Festival Hub garden this family friendly space will explore, play, and create with the natural wonders of Country. Jarjum Life Museum (JLM): Botanica will connect with Traditional Owners, Elders, community members and jarjum &#8230; <a href="/event/jarjums-life-museum-botanica/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Deep dive into the floral worlds of Jinibara and Kabi Kabi Country with Jarjum Life Museum&rsquo;s Botanica work. Popping up at the Festival Hub garden this family friendly space will explore, play, and create with the natural wonders of Country. Jarjum Life Museum (JLM): Botanica will connect with Traditional Owners, Elders, community members and jarjum to create a hands-on...</p>
<p><a href="/event/jarjums-life-museum-botanica/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Story time with Codie &#038; Ryan</title>
		<link>/event/story-time-with-codie-ryan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 22:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4850</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Join Codie and Ryan from Sunshine Coast Libraries for a rousing story time aboard the Troubadour Wagon in the Festival Hub garden. Showcasing classic stories and rhymes plus a few new ones for you to discover. If you love a good story or rhyme, you’ve come to the right place — you and your little &#8230; <a href="/event/story-time-with-codie-ryan/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Join Codie and Ryan from Sunshine Coast Libraries for a rousing story time aboard the Troubadour Wagon in the Festival Hub garden. Showcasing classic stories and rhymes plus a few new ones for you to discover. If you love a good story or rhyme, you&rsquo;ve come to the right place &mdash; you and your little one are guaranteed lots of fun and laughter.</p>
<p><a href="/event/story-time-with-codie-ryan/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dear Reader: a celebration of readers, writers and libraries</title>
		<link>/event/dear-reader-a-celebration-of-readers-writers-and-libraries/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 03:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4792</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Read, listen, learn and connect with your community over your shared love of literature.Sunshine Coast Council Libraries are bringing together writers, readers, and creatives to share the love of stories for one big day at the Beerwah Heart Precinct. Meet and mingle with successful local authors, join exciting storytelling sessions, hear compelling First Nations stories, &#8230; <a href="/event/dear-reader-a-celebration-of-readers-writers-and-libraries/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Read, listen, learn and connect with your community over your shared love of literature.Sunshine Coast Council Libraries are bringing together writers, readers, and creatives to share the love of stories for one big day at the Beerwah Heart Precinct. Meet and mingle with successful local authors, join exciting storytelling sessions, hear compelling First Nations stories, find your next great read...</p>
<p><a href="/event/dear-reader-a-celebration-of-readers-writers-and-libraries/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tallo-Billa: Ocean Fieldtrip (sold out)</title>
		<link>/event/tallo-billa-ocean-fieldtrip/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 02:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4775</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Field Trip is an experimental national research symposium featuring creative practice at the intersection of art, science, technology and the environment. The creative team will introduce the experimental technology and collaborative methodologies underpinning the Beeyali project, creating an immersive audio-visual experience that highlights the interconnectivity of life within marine environments. Delving into the multifaceted processes and &#8230; <a href="/event/tallo-billa-ocean-fieldtrip/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Field Trip is an experimental national research symposium featuring creative practice at the intersection of art, science, technology and the environment. The creative team will introduce the experimental technology and collaborative methodologies underpinning the Beeyali project, creating an immersive audio-visual experience that highlights the interconnectivity of life within marine environments.</p>
<p><a href="/event/tallo-billa-ocean-fieldtrip/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Living Waters: A Short Film Event</title>
		<link>/event/living-waters-a-short-film-event/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 02:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4769</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Join us for LIVING WATERS: A SHORT FILM EVENT where we will be exploring humanity&#8217;s unique, spiritual and ecological relationship to water, featuring: TWO KINDS OF WATER (Senegal, Africa) tells the story of the unbreakable bond between a fisherman and his wife as they fight to keep their young family afloat in one of Africa’s most vulnerable fishing &#8230; <a href="/event/living-waters-a-short-film-event/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Join us for LIVING WATERS: A SHORT FILM EVENT where we will be exploring humanity&rsquo;s unique, spiritual and ecological relationship to water, featuring: TWO KINDS OF WATER (Senegal, Africa) tells the story of the unbreakable bond between a fisherman and his wife as they fight to keep their young family afloat in one of Africa&rsquo;s most vulnerable fishing villages. In John Harvey&rsquo;s award winning film...</p>
<p><a href="/event/living-waters-a-short-film-event/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conversations with men (sold out)</title>
		<link>/event/conversations-with-men/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 01:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4630</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Conversations With Men (CWM) is an exploration of masculinity, vulnerability and the tender connection between men and their childhood selves. Moderated by writer, broadcaster and feminist community builder Clementine Ford. CWM invites five local Sunshine Coast men to speak to the boys they used to be about the men they learned to become. In this &#8230; <a href="/event/conversations-with-men/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Conversations With Men (CWM) is an exploration of masculinity, vulnerability and the tender connection between men and their childhood selves. Moderated by writer, broadcaster and feminist community builder Clementine Ford. CWM invites five local Sunshine Coast men to speak to the boys they used to be about the men they learned to become. In this intimate space, and through the generosity of these...</p>
<p><a href="/event/conversations-with-men/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
