<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Visual Art &#8211; Horizon Festival | Sunshine Coast</title>
	<atom:link href="/news/whats-on/category/visual-art/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Presenting 10 days and nights of visual art, music, theatre, dance, words + ideas, film and creative workshops; inspired by the stories and beauty of the Sunshine Coast.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 05:56:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Sunshine Coast Art Prize 2023</title>
		<link>/event/sunshine-coast-art-prize-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4879</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Regional Gallery of the Sunshine Coast presents a dynamic exhibition program featuring leading national and local artists, complemented by immersive public programs, educational programs, tours, and events. The Gallery Store highlights regional and national artisans, with a focus on local, hand-crafted items and a curated Pop-Up Feature Artisan program with every exhibition. The national &#8230; <a href="/event/sunshine-coast-art-prize-2023/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Regional Gallery of the Sunshine Coast presents a dynamic exhibition program featuring leading national and local artists, complemented by immersive public programs, educational programs, tours, and events. The Gallery Store highlights regional and national artisans, with a focus on local, hand-crafted items and a curated Pop-Up Feature Artisan program with every exhibition.</p>
<p><a href="/event/sunshine-coast-art-prize-2023/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Skateboard Art Workshop</title>
		<link>/event/skateboard-art-workshop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4874</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Paint your own skateboard, whether you skate or don’t! This workshop is suitable for a solo mission/opportunity to meet new people, a date night between lovers or friends and everyone else in between. All materials provided, just bring yourself! About the Artist Fat Dog transcends the mundane through creation, typically with acrylic on skateboards.  A &#8230; <a href="/event/skateboard-art-workshop/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Paint your own skateboard, whether you skate or don&rsquo;t! This workshop is suitable for a solo mission/opportunity to meet new people, a date night between lovers or friends and everyone else in between. All materials provided, just bring yourself! Fat Dog transcends the mundane through creation, typically with acrylic on skateboards. A wildly fun and colourful caricaturist who exudes a passion for...</p>
<p><a href="/event/skateboard-art-workshop/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>hotmess (sold out)</title>
		<link>/event/hotmess/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 23:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4862</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HOTMESS is a decadent life drawing experience designed to ignite your creative fire and release you from normality. Be prepared to be immersed in a fictional world of costume, sound, lighting and performance used to playfully nudge one to question the fabric of life through emotional experiences. HOTMESS thrives on the edge of exploring ideas &#8230; <a href="/event/hotmess/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HOTMESS is a decadent life drawing experience designed to ignite your creative fire and release you from normality. Be prepared to be immersed in a fictional world of costume, sound, lighting and performance used to playfully nudge one to question the fabric of life through emotional experiences. HOTMESS thrives on the edge of exploring ideas that are cheeky, evocative and conceptual...</p>
<p><a href="/event/hotmess/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WARP</title>
		<link>/event/warp/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 10:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4839</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WARP is a Jack MacRae exhibition, presenting in an old abandoned jail. An explosion of distilled geometric forms, Jack’s new body of work takes on an expanded painting practice — rationalised, brutalised, explored, and expanded. Born from solitary, WARP is a raw, lost-in-thought and hopeful portrayal of what’s to come. Lock yourself in and throw &#8230; <a href="/event/warp/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WARP is a Jack MacRae exhibition, presenting in an old abandoned jail. An explosion of distilled geometric forms, Jack&rsquo;s new body of work takes on an expanded painting practice &mdash; rationalised, brutalised, explored, and expanded. Born from solitary, WARP is a raw, lost-in-thought and hopeful portrayal of what&rsquo;s to come. Lock yourself in and throw away the key. WARP will launch on the opening night...</p>
<p><a href="/event/warp/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Your Local Photo Club</title>
		<link>/event/your-local-photo-club/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 10:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4831</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Your Local Photo Club is a collaborative photo exhibition showcasing the works of Sunshine Coast and Brisbane based artists. The exhibition celebrates place and explores the motives for shooting film in today&#8217;s digital age. This one-night-only exhibition is a reflection on the role of film photography in contemporary art — featuring a diverse range of &#8230; <a href="/event/your-local-photo-club/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Your Local Photo Club is a collaborative photo exhibition showcasing the works of Sunshine Coast and Brisbane based artists. The exhibition celebrates place and explores the motives for shooting film in today&rsquo;s digital age. This one-night-only exhibition is a reflection on the role of film photography in contemporary art &mdash; featuring a diverse range of subjects, styles, and themes.</p>
<p><a href="/event/your-local-photo-club/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tallo-Billa (sold out)</title>
		<link>/event/tallo-billa/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 02:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4781</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[For Horizon Festival 2023, the Beeyali team invites attendees on a dusk ocean journey on board Sunreef’s Whale One, to listen underwater and experience cymatic visualisations of humpback whale songs. The field trip commences in Mooloolaba, where humpback whales annually migrate and rear their calves before returning to Antarctic waters and concludes with an original &#8230; <a href="/event/tallo-billa/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For Horizon Festival 2023, the Beeyali team invites attendees on a dusk ocean journey on board Sunreef&rsquo;s Whale One, to listen underwater and experience cymatic visualisations of humpback whale songs. The field trip commences in Mooloolaba, where humpback whales annually migrate and rear their calves before returning to Antarctic waters and concludes with an original immersive experience of the new...</p>
<p><a href="/event/tallo-billa/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You Are Neither Here Nor There: Sam Cranstoun</title>
		<link>/event/you-are-neither-here-nor-there-sam-cranstoun/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 01:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4759</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You Are Neither Here Nor There brings together four projects made during the first decade of Queensland artist Sam Cranstoun’s research-driven practice. The subject matter reflects the artist’s interest in lesser-known aspects of significant twentieth-century figures and events. Mies Van Der Rohe’s Farnsworth House, the Memphis motel where Martin Luther King was assassinated, and the &#8230; <a href="/event/you-are-neither-here-nor-there-sam-cranstoun/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You Are Neither Here Nor There brings together four projects made during the first decade of Queensland artist Sam Cranstoun&rsquo;s research-driven practice. The subject matter reflects the artist&rsquo;s interest in lesser-known aspects of significant twentieth-century figures and events. Mies Van Der Rohe&rsquo;s Farnsworth House, the Memphis motel where Martin Luther King was assassinated, and the life of...</p>
<p><a href="/event/you-are-neither-here-nor-there-sam-cranstoun/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Glambour (sold out)</title>
		<link>/event/glambour/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4754</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Glambour is the launch party for two exhibitions at The Old Ambo: Unapologetically Dressed and Nonsensual. Expect a night of glamour, drag, music, costumes, and a lip sync battle — don’t forget to dress up! The evening will be hosted by this lot, so you know it’ll be a hoot: Andrea Kirwin, Jess Harlen, Ketakii &#8230; <a href="/event/glambour/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Glambour is the launch party for two exhibitions at The Old Ambo: Unapologetically Dressed and Nonsensual. Expect a night of glamour, drag, music, costumes, and a lip sync battle &mdash; don&rsquo;t forget to dress up! The evening will be hosted by this lot, so you know it&rsquo;ll be a hoot: Andrea Kirwin, Jess Harlen, Ketakii Jewson-Brown, Shaye Hardisty, Fat Dog, Jordyn Burnett, Fiona Harding, and heaps more.</p>
<p><a href="/event/glambour/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unapologetically Dressed</title>
		<link>/event/unapologetically-dressed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4750</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Unapologetically Dressed was born out of Mill Street Fashion Walk — an Instagram page dedicated to a necessity to document fashion on the streets of Nambour. Ketakii Jewson-Brown and Shaye Hardsity of ShayeKet Productions began scoping out the street style of Nambour back in 2019. As the fashion capital of the Sunshine Coast, Nambour’s streets &#8230; <a href="/event/unapologetically-dressed/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unapologetically Dressed was born out of Mill Street Fashion Walk &mdash; an Instagram page dedicated to a necessity to document fashion on the streets of Nambour. Ketakii Jewson-Brown and Shaye Hardsity of ShayeKet Productions began scoping out the street style of Nambour back in 2019. As the fashion capital of the Sunshine Coast, Nambour&rsquo;s streets showcase a visual smorgasbord full of eclectic...</p>
<p><a href="/event/unapologetically-dressed/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nonsensual</title>
		<link>/event/nonsensual/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ben]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.horizonfestival.com.au/?post_type=event&#038;p=4744</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Set your senses into overdrive with this wildly fun, colourful and absurd exhibition. Nonsensual is a non-censored and nonsensical art display. In layman’s terms: Nonsensual is an uncensored exhibition, featuring three unapologetic artists — Fat Dog, Spirit You, and Jordyn Burnett — on their journey for meaning in a world that makes no f**cking sense. &#8230; <a href="/event/nonsensual/">More ></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Set your senses into overdrive with this wildly fun, colourful and absurd exhibition. Nonsensual is a non-censored and nonsensical art display. In layman&rsquo;s terms: Nonsensual is an uncensored exhibition, featuring three unapologetic artists &mdash; Fat Dog, Spirit You, and Jordyn Burnett &mdash; on their journey for meaning in a world that makes no f**cking sense.</p>
<p><a href="/event/nonsensual/" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
